oneclickroot.com 2018-03-04

# Privacy Policy

## **ONECLICKROOT.COM PRIVACY POLICY**

All contents copyright © 2018\. All rights reserved.

* * *

#### **Introduction**

Thank you for visiting ONECLICKROOT.COM and, if applicable, choosing to use our Software or any Services. We try to make our Privacy Policy easy to understand so that you are informed as to how we use your information.  This Privacy Policy, like our Terms of Service, is an integral part of using our Service and Software. You must completely agree to our Privacy Policy to use our Site, Software and Service.  If you are under 18 please stop using our Service immediately.

#### **Definitions**

Throughout this Privacy Policy, we may use certain words or phrases, and it is important that you understand the meaning of them.  The list is not all-encompassing and no definition should be considered binding to the point that it renders this Privacy Policy nonsensical:

  * “One Click Root”, “we” or “us” refers to the business which owns this website One Click Root, our Site, Software, or any associated Services, depending on the context of the usage;
  * “Service(s)” refers to the services that we provide through our Site and our Software;
  * “Software” refers to our root software available for purchase and download through our Site;
  * “Site” refers to our website, [oneclickroot.com](https://www.oneclickroot.com/);
  * “You” or “user” refers to you, the person who is entering into this Agreement with One Click Root, the owner and operator of ONECLICKROOT.COM.

#### **Information Collected**

Identifying Information Submitted by You  
You are not required to register to view our site.  However, registration is required to purchase our Software, when registering we may ask you to submit your name and email to us.  If you wish to purchase our Software you must provide your credit card information to our third party payment processor SafeCart.  We do not collect or store your payment information, such information is subject to SafeCart’s Terms of Service and Privacy Policy.  
Non-Identifying Information  
Whenever you visit our Site, we may collect non-identifying information from you, such as your IP address, interactions with the Site and Service, referring URL, browser, operating system, cookie information, usage, data transferred and Internet Service Provider.  Without a subpoena, voluntary compliance on the part of your Internet Service Provider, or additional records from a third party such as your wireless provider, this information alone cannot usually be used to identify you.

#### **Use of Your Information**

We will never sell, transfer or give your information to a third party without your permission. However, you agree that we may use your information:

  * To enhance or improve our users’ experiences.
  * To send emails about the other products, news and updates.
  * To send emails and newsletters about our Site or respond to inquiries.
  * To send emails about third party products or services.

Additionally, we may give your information to law enforcement if we are compelled to by a court order, if there has been a violation of any US laws, Canadian or EU laws or if a violation of the Terms of Service, Software License Agreement or Privacy Policy has occurred.

#### **Accessing, Editing, and Removing Your Information**

Once you have submitted information to our Site you may be able to edit your information through your account. If you want your information to be removed from our database or wish to inquire on the data we have collected from you please contact us at [support@ONECLICKROOT.COM](mailto:support@ONECLICKROOT.COM) .  Although some changes may occur immediately, information may still be stored in a web browser’s cache.  We take no responsibility for stored information in your cache, or in other devices that may store information, and disclaim all liability of such.  Additionally, after deletion of your information your data may be stored by us for up to 2 years for legal liability purposes.

#### **Cookies**

We use cookies to save your preferences and to keep track of advertisements.  For this reason, you must have cookies enabled in your browser to use our Site and Services.  Additionally, some or all of our cookies may be accessible by third parties.

#### **Third Party Access to Your Information**

Although you are entering into an Agreement with One Click Root to disclose your information to us, we do use third party individuals and organizations to assist us, including contractors, web hosts, and others.  
Throughout the course of our provision of our Services to you, we may delegate our authority to collect, access, use, and disseminate your information.  For example, when you submit a form with personally identifiable information to us, that information will be disseminated or forwarded through our Service to your local law enforcement agency.  
It is therefore necessary that you grant the third parties we may use in the course of our business the same rights that you afford us under this Privacy Policy.  For this reason, you hereby agree that for every authorization which you grant to us in this Privacy Policy, you also grant to any third party that we may hire, contract, or otherwise retain the services of for the purpose of operating, maintaining, repairing, or otherwise improving or preserving our website or its underlying files or systems.  You agree not to hold us liable for the actions of any of these third parties, even if we would normally be held vicariously liable for their actions, and that you must take legal action against them directly should they commit any tort or other actionable wrong against you.  The following is a non-exhaustive list of other entities that we may store, share, or transfer your information with:

  * SafeCart

#### **Law Enforcement**

You agree that we may disclose your information to authorities if compelled to by a court order.  Additionally, you agree that we may disclose your information if we reasonably believe that you have violated a US law, Canadian law or the terms of our Terms of Service, Software License Agreement or Privacy Policy or if we believe that a third party is at risk of bodily harm.   In the event that we receive a subpoena affecting your privacy, we may elect to notify you to give you an opportunity to file a motion to quash the subpoena, or we may attempt to quash it ourselves, but we are not obligated to do either.  We may also proactively report you and release your information without receiving any request to third parties where we believe that it is proper to do so for legal reasons, such as instances where we believe your publications violate any law of Canada or any other country having jurisdiction over us, our Site, Services, or our Terms of Service.  You release us from any damages that may arise from or relate to the release of your information to a request from law enforcement agencies or private litigants.  We may release your information under the conditions listed in this paragraph whether it is to individuals or entities and to any state or Federal authorities within the United States, or elsewhere.

#### **Commercial and Non-Commercial Communications**

By providing information to the Site that forms the basis of communication with you, such as contact information, you waive all rights to file complaints concerning unsolicited email from us, since you have agreed to such communication by providing your information to us.  However, you may be able to unsubscribe from certain communications by notifying One Click Root that you no longer wish to receive solicitations or information and we will endeavour to remove you from our database where you have the right to request this under our Agreement, Privacy Policy, or applicable law, or where we voluntarily decide to grant the request.

#### **Third Parties**

One Click Root may post links to third party websites on our Site, which may include information that we have no control over.  When accessing a third party site through our Site or Service, you acknowledge that you are aware that these third party websites are not screened for privacy or security issues by us, and you release us from any liability for the conduct of these third party websites.  
Please be aware that this Privacy Policy, and any other policies in place, in addition to any amendments, does not create rights enforceable by third parties.  One Click Root bears no responsibility for the information collected or used by any advertiser or third party website. You must review their Terms of Service and Privacy to understand how their information collection practices work.

#### **Security Measures**

We take certain measures to enhance the security of our Site and Services.  To this end, we use SSL Certificates.  However, we make no guarantees as to the security or privacy of your information.  It is in our interest to keep our website secure, but we recommend that you use anti-virus software, routine credit checks, firewalls, and other precautions to protect yourself from security and privacy threats.

#### **Your California Privacy Rights**

One Click Root permits residents of the State of California to use its Service, and complies with the California Business and Professions Code §§ 22575-22579.  If you are a California resident you may request certain information regarding our disclosure of personal information to any third parties for their direct marketing purposes.  Various provisions throughout this Privacy Policy address requirements of the Californian privacy statutes. Although we do not disseminate your information to third parties without permission, you must presume that we collect electronic information from all visitors. You may contact us at [support@ONECLICKROOT.COM](mailto:support@ONECLICKROOT.COM) with any questions.

#### **Personal Information Protection and Electronic Documents Act (PIPEDA)**

One Click Root is a Canadian company and we fully intend on complying with PIPEDA and its 10 principles. Various provisions throughout this Privacy Policy address the requirements of PIPEDA.  If you are a Canadian citizen and have questions or concerns regarding your privacy or our collection practices, please contact us at support@oneclickroot.com.

#### **COPPA Compliance**

We intend to fully comply with COPPA and international laws respecting children’s privacy.  Therefore, we do not collect or process any information for any persons under the age of 18.  If you are under 18 and using our Site or Service, please stop immediately and do not submit any information to us.

#### **International Transfer**

Your information may be transferred to – and maintained on – computers located outside of your state, province, country, or other governmental jurisdiction where the privacy laws may not be as protective as those in your jurisdiction.  We may transfer personal information to the Canada or elsewhere and process it there.  Your consent to this Privacy Policy followed by your submission of such information represents your agreement to that transfer.

#### **Amendments**

Like our Terms of Service, we may amend this Privacy Policy from time to time.  When we amend this Privacy Policy, we will place a note on our Site or we may contact you.  You must agree to the amendments as a condition of your continued use of our Site and Service.  If you do not agree, you must immediately cease using our Site and Service and notify us of your refusal to agree by e-mailing us at support@oneclickroot.com.  
Last Modified: November 14, 2012
